## Daniel Oyewole ALABI HND

13, Iyana Cele Bus stop road, Apete Ibadan Oyo State oyewolealabi@outlook.com 08166020057

## **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Detailed oriented and highly-organized individual with progressive experience in Finance and hotel administration. Well versed in providing front office services in any kind of organization and with the ability to grasp new concepts swiftly and adapt to changing business needs. Displays confidence in roles which require important level of diligence, dedicated team work and advance problem solving skills with demonstrated ability to meet deadlines and exceed goals.

## **PERSONAL DETAIL**

Gender: Male
Nationality: Nigerian
Date of Birth: 3<sup>rd</sup> July 1993

### **CORE SKILLS/COMPETENCIES**

- Proficiency in Microsoft Office Suite
- Strong Verbal/Written Communication skills
- Meeting deadline in a Time Efficient manner
- Excellent Customer service
- Excellent Customer Retention

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## ALAKOTO JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL - Olodi-Apapa, Lagos

**Computer Teacher** (NYSC-Primary Assignment)

October 2018-September 2019

- Teaching computer studies
- Handling all the computer practical for the students
- Handling all the schools secretarial work

### **KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Sharpened my Skill of Teaching
- Developed ability to multitask

## **ACCESS BANK PLC** – Apapa Wharf, Lagos

Relieve Staff (Customer care officer)

March - April 2019

- Resolving Customers complaint
- BVN Validation and Registration
- ATM Cash sorting and Loading

### KEY ACCOMPLISHMENT

- Ability to work with a team
- Customer Care skill
- Sharpened my skill to make use of some computer banking applications

# **BLUE PETALS HOTELS AND SUITES –** Ede, Osun state **Operations Manager**

June 2015 - April 2016

- Supervise the daily activity of the organization
- Be up and doing in the inspection of work done by staffs
- Submit a timely quarterly reports of activities to the CEO

### **KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Sharpened my managerial skills
- Ability to work and impact
- Got the hotel verified by Google thereby increasing search availability and guest reviews.
- Earned reputation for strong work ethics, honesty and 100% commitment to given task

## ABM HOTELS LTD - Ede, Osun State

## Finance Officer

November 2014 - May 2015

- Receiving and recording daily sales and expenditures of the establishment
- Bank Reconciliation duty
- Payments of staffs salary

### **KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Successfully worked with the Finance department of the organization
- Assisted in solving out bank reconciliation reviews

## **EDUCATION**

THE FEDERAL POLYTECHNIC EDE – Ede, Osun State 2018 HND – Banking and Finance	2016 –
OMOWUMI COMPREHENSIVE COLLEGE – Ede, Osun State Senior Secondary Certificate Examinations (SSCE)	2004 – 2010
GLORY OF GOD NURSERY & PRIMARY SCHOOL – Ejigbo, Osun State 2004 First school Living Certificate (FSLC)	1998 –

## Oyewole Daniel Alabi 08166020057

TRAINING & CERTIFICATION	
<ul> <li>National Institute of management (NIM) (In view)</li> <li>National Youth Service Corps (NYSC) – (Discharge Certificate)         <ul> <li>2019</li> </ul> </li> <li>Certificate of Professional Development (Human Resource management)         (Envirofly Consulting UK)</li> </ul>	2019
LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCES	
<ul> <li>PRESIDENT - NYSC CDS, Apapa Lagos</li> <li>PRESIDING OFFICER - INEC Apapa LG</li> <li>PRESIDENT - Student Union Government         The Federal Polytechnic Ede, Osun State 2018     </li> <li>TREASURER - Male Hall of Residence         The Federal Polytechnic, Ede Osun State 2013     </li> <li>CLASS GOVERNOR - Banking and Finance Department         The Federal Polytechnic, Ede Osun State     </li> </ul>	2019 2019 2017 - 2012 –

## REFEREES

> Available on Request